A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Audiovisual materials, Series 39 FA756
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, Political Films, 1945-1976; 1
  - 1968
    - Crime Control Week, 1968 December; Sound, Color, 2 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1112)
      TV spot on the State Police sent to all local TV stations for use during the week of 1968 December 2.
    - 1968 Year-End Interview with Gabe Pressman, 1968 December 20; Sound, Color, 6 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1362)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller interview by Gabe Pressman, topics include equal opportunity, race, Richard Nixon, 1968 struggles, amd financial issues.
    - Nelson Rockefeller Speech at Polish Home Picnic in Auburn, New York, 1968; Silent, Color, 5 minutes; 8mm film (Reel AV 1246)
      Nelson Rockefeller speech during presidential campaign filmed by Mrs. Dorcas Tucker of North Carolina.
  - 1969
    - Message to Legislature, 1969 January 8; Silent, Color, 40 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1943, Reel AV 1942)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller annual message to the New York State legislature, Albany, New York.
    - 1969 Town Meeting with Governor Rockefeller, 1969 January 29; Sound, Color, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1748)
      Town meetings at Roberson Center in Binghamton, Nre York and Howard Johnson in Elmira, New York.
    - A New Crown for the Empire State, 1969 May; Sound, Color, 25 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1857)
      NBC-TV News piece about the reconstruction of the South Mall in Albany, NY. Program was broadcast on New York Illustrated, 1969 May.
    - Today Show Interview with Nelson A. Rockefeller - NBC-TV, 1969 May 13; Sound, Color, 9 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1679)
      Aline Saarinen of NBC-TV News interviews Nelson Rockefeller about gift of primitive art collection to the Metropolitan Museum of Art, intercut with scenes of exhibition and featured pieces.
    - Rockefeller Visit to Binghamton, Broome County, New York, 1969 November 19; Silent, Color, 16 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1363)
      NAR visits proposed site of new state building, speaks at rally
    - 1969 Year-End Review, 1969 December 10; Sound, Color, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1101)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller interviewed by Glover Delany, president of New York State Broadcasters Association, and filmed by Hal Posner.
  - 1970
    - 1970 Rockefeller Campaign Commercials, Sound, Black and white; 16mm film (Reel AV 1837)
      Compilation reel of tv spots from Nelson A. Rockefeller's 1970 gubernatorial campaign; 25 different commercials including issues about budget, SUNY system extension, importance of growing businesses, limiting taxes, drug policies, etc.
    - Annual Message to the Legislature, 1970 January 7; Sound, Color, 50 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 2857, Reel AV 2858)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller's annual message to the New York State legislature, Albany, New York.
    - Bob Hope Dinner with Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1970 March 20; Silent, Color, 5 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1575)
      From NBC-TV.
    - 1970 Miss Universe Parade, 1970 August 8; Sound, Color, 10 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1248)
      UPI News footage of Nelson A. Rockefeller hosting Marisol Malaret, Miss Universe 1970, in New York City at a parade and a luncheon.
    - Hudson Highlands State Park Dedication, 1970 May 23; 16mm film; Sound, Black and white (Reel AV 2937)
    - Election Night Coverage, 1970 November 3; Sound, Color, 4 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1250)
      NBC-TV coverage of NAR at the Roosevelt Hotel in New York City.
  - 1971-1976
    - Governor Rockefeller at Joint Session of Legislature Opening Day, 1971 January 6; Sound, Color, 29 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1389)
      Filmed close-ups from Nelson A. Rockefeller speech.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Inauguration, 1971 January 1; Sound, Color, 29 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1757)
      Footage from inauguration in Albany, New York.
    - Governor Rockefeller Nominates Richard Nixon, 1972 August; Sound, Color, 14 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1686)
      Nelson A, Rockefeller nominates Richard Nixon as presidential candidate at Republican National Convention in Miami, Florida.
    - Annual Message to the Legislature, 1973 January 3; Sound, Color, 60 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1774, Reel AV 1816)
      Footage of Governor Rockefeller's annual message to the New York State Legislature, filmed in the Assembly Chamber at the Capital Building in Albany, New York.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Press Conference on Narcotics, 1973 January 22; Sound, Color, 30 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1078)
      Press conference with Governor Rockefeller, Rev. Oberia D. Dempsey, Rev. Earl B. Moore, Glester Hinds, Dr. George W. McMurray, and Dr. Robert W. Baird.
      Video transfer accessible: AV 10605
    - George Washington Inauguration Day Ceremony, 1976 April 30; Sound, Black and white, 4 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1096)
      Footage of speech by Vice President Nelson A Rockefeller at reenactment festivities.
    - The View From the Bottom, c.1970s; Sound, Black and white, 18 minutes; 16mm film (Reel AV 1074)
      Collection of interviews about social welfare and urban programs coordinated by Nelson Rockefeller.
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, Political Video material, 1960-1975; 2
  Loosely arranged by year.
  - 1960
    - Four Stars on the Issues, 1960 October 19; 2 inch videotape; Sound, Black and white, 18 minutes (Box 32, Reel AV 10606)
      Unedited videotape. First 2:30 minutes no image, low volume. Program begins at 3:20.
      Discussion with Vice President Richard Nixon, New York State Govenor Nelson A. Rockefeller, and New York Senators Jacob K. Javits and Kenneth B. Keating on the issues New York citizens have stated are important to them in this election. CBS Production # 10-2785-1019
  - 1961
    - Rockefeller - Republican Committee - Take 1 (NAR Endorses Louis Lefkowitz for NYC Mayor), 1961 September 30; Sound, Black and white, 5 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 21, Reel AV 11406)
    - NAR: Vote For Louis Lefkowitz, NYC Mayor (For Change) - Take 3, 1961 September 21; Sound, Black and white, 40 seconds; 2 inch videotape (Box 18, Reel AV 11500)
    - NAR: Vote For Louis Lefkowitz, NYC Mayor, 1961 September 21; Sound, Black and white, 1 min. 20 sec.; 2 inch videotape (Box 15, Reel AV 11469)
    - NAR: Vote For Louis Lefkowitz, NYC Mayor (For Crime) - Take 3, 1961 September 21; Sound, Black and white, 40 seconds; 2 inch videotape (Box 16, Reel AV 11473)
  - 1962
    - Election Eve: Wrap-Up!, 1962 November 5; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 22, Reel AV 10596)
      Post-election roundtable discussion with the Rockefeller team summarizing the entire campaign. Speakers include: Marcus G. Christ, John P. Lomenzo, Louis J. Lefkowitz, Malcolm Wilson, Jacob K. Javits, and Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    - Pre-Convention Legislative Reports I, 1962 April 23; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 28, Reel AV 10602)
      Compilation reel with Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller reporting on recent New York State legislative actions, includings economic growth, housing, education, law enforcement, among others. Each segment is approximately 3 minutes in duration.
    - Pre-Convention Legislative Reports II, 1962 October; Sound, Black and white, 55 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 47, Reel AV 10636)
      Compilation reel with Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller and his campaign team reporting on recent New York State legislative actions.
      Program begins with 4 minutes of black. Intermittent black between segments.
    - Godkin Lectures Number 1: The Future of Federalism, Part 1, 1962 February 7; 2 inch videotape; Sound, Black and white, 50 minutes (Box 69, Reel AV 10643)
      Program begins at 2:40.
      Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller presents the first of three lectures on 'The Future of Federalism' as part of the Godkin Lecture Series at Harvard University.
    - Godkin Lectures Number 1: The Future of Federalism, Part 2, 1962 February 7; 2 inch videotape; Sound, Black and white, 14 minutes (Box 71, Reel AV 10645)
      Program begins at 2:14.
    - Godkin Lectures Number 2: The Future of Federalism, Part 1, 1962 February 8; Sound, Black and white, 35 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 36, Reel AV 10610)
      Image is black for last minute of recording, audio only.
      Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller presents the second of three lectures on 'The Future of Federalism' as part of the Godkin Lecture Series at Harvard University.
    - Godkin Lectures Number 2: The Future of Federalism, Part 2, 1962 February 8; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 37, Reel AV 10611)
    - Godkin Lectures Number 3: The Future of Federalism, Part 1, 1962 February 8; 2 inch videotape; Sound, Black and white, 45 minutes (Box 70, Reel AV 10644)
      Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller presents the third of three lectures on 'The Future of Federalism' as part of the Godkin Lecture Series at Harvard University.
    - Godkin Lectures Number 3: The Future of Federalism, Part 2, 1962 February 8; Sound, Black and white, 50 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 60, Reel AV 10612)
    - Victory Vanguard - 1962 Campaign, Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 61, Reel AV 10621)
      Episode of Victory Vanguard that looks at the 1962 state election, with Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller. Program sponsored by the New York Republican State Committee.
    - School Aid - Take 7, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1962 October 13; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute 35 seconds; 2 inch videotape (Box 10, Reel AV 11417)
  - 1963
    - Education - College Education Booklet - Take 7, 1963 July 3; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute 45 seconds; 2 inch videotape (Box 20, Reel AV 11514)
      NAR urges viewers to obtain a copy of "Help For Your College Education, 1963-1964."
  - 1964
    - 1964 California Primary: The Extremists, 1964 May 27; 2 inch videotape; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes (Box 23, Reel AV 10597)
      Program features Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dave Garroway, and others discussing the efforts of right-wing extremists to influence and/or control the California Republican State Party.
    - Executive Chamber, Number 1: How Much Education?, November 1964; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 29, Reel AV 10603)
      New York State Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller and education professionals discusses the need for education and the state of the New York State schools.
    - Executive Chamber, Number 3: In The Name of the People, 1964 December; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 48, Reel AV 10637)
      In his annual message to the legislature, Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller recommends solutions to the problems facing the people of New York State. These include: issues of education on all levels, water pollution abatement, per capita aid, traffic safety, and full crew law. The Governor also relates how state laws are made.
    - Oregon Campaign - Citizens' Questions and Answers, 1964; Sound, Black and white, 38 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 27, Reel AV 10601)
      Oregon citizens meet one-on-one with Nelson A. Rockefeller in an outdoor forum to ask their questions.
    - 1964 California Republican Presidential Primary: Report to Rockefeller, Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 52, Reel AV 10613)
      Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller presents his views on the issues of interest and concern to the Republican voters of California. He is joined by Senator John McCarthy, Assemblyman Milton Marks, Assembly man John Veneman, Assemblyman George Milias, and Assemblyman William Bagley.
    - Governor Nelson Rockefeller on Liquor Law Reform, 1964 April 9; Sound, Black and white, 13 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 62, Reel AV 10622)
      Governor Nelson Rockefeller discusses liquor law reform after corruption occurs in New York State. Program presented and paid for by N.Y. State Citizens Committee for Liquor Reform. Air date: 1964 April 11.
    - Governor Rockefeller Campaign Compilation Reel - 2, 1964 February 11; Sound, Black and white, 11 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 20, Reel AV 11516)
      Includes the following spots: Cuba, Small Business, Leadership Gap, Economic Growth, and the Republican Party.
    - Governor Rockefeller Campaign Compilation Reel - 1, 1964 January 18; Sound, Black and white, 8 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 20, Reel AV 11515)
      Includes the following spots: Welfare, Withdrawing Recognition, and the United Nations.
    - Oregon Campaign Film, 1964; Sound, Black and white, 26 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 65, Reel AV 10625)
      Film with Nelson A. Rockefeller and Happy Rockefeller campaigning in Oregon.
      Contains silent footage at end of program.
    - Meet Nelson Rockefeller, 1964 March 9; 2 inch videotape; Sound, Black and white, 60 minutes (Box 68, Reel AV 10642)
      Audio buzz throughout.
      A primary television special for New Hampshire voters on WMUR-TV. Program includes "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" and candidate Rockefeller speaks directly to the televison viewers.
  - 1965
    - Executive Chamber, Number 4: The View from the Governor's Chair, 1965 January 26; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 46, Reel AV 10635)
      New York State Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller reports in detail about the New York State annual budget. Several key figures speak about their requested funding including: Dr. William J. Ronan from the Tri-State Transportation Committee, Lawrence W. Pierce from the Division of Youth, J. Burch McMorran, Supt. of Public Works, George K. Wyman, Commissioner of Social Welfare, John Hathorn from the Office of Indian Affairs, Dr. James E. Allen, Commissioner of Education, and Dr. Henry Brill, Director of Pilgrim State Hospital. Captain John C. Miller of the Oneida Barracks N.Y. State Police requests a $150 increase for dog food.
    - Executive Chamber, Number 6: Transportation Tangle, 1965 March; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 25, Reel AV 10599)
      New York State Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller discusses the creation of the Metropolitan Transportation Authority (MTA) and the Federal Department of Transportation.
    - Executive Chamber, Number 7: Troubled Mind, 1965 April; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 26, Reel AV 10600)
      New York State Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller and health professionals discusses mental illness, the need to create new facilities, and the progress of New York State hospitals.
    - Executive Chamber, Number 8: A Walk in the Glen, 1965 May; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 45, Reel AV 10634)
      New York State Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller profiles Watkins Glen, New York, to show a small community and its problems and achievements. Some stories from locals and a visit to the Watkins Glen cemetery and Watkins Glen National Park.
    - Governor Rockefeller Reviews the 1965 Legislature, 1965 June 24; Sound, Black and white, 15 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 34, Reel AV 10608)
      Begins with 1 minute of NBC test pattern and tones. Image quality poor. Image progressively gets worse throughout duration of tape.
      Govenor Nelson A. Rockefeller gives his opinions about what has transpired in the New York state capitol during the 1965 Legislative session.
  - 1966
    - Thomas E. Dewey Talks About Governor Nelson Rockefeller, 1966; Sound, Black and white, 16 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 53, Reel AV 10614)
      Silent footage at beginning. Program begins at 1 minute 40 seconds.
      From the Cotillion Room at the Sheraton Hotel in Rochester, New York, the former three term governor of New York State, Thomas E. Dewey, encourages Republicans to vote to re-elect Nelson Rockefeller.
    - Question Card - Take 14, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 20, Reel AV 11511)
    - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller's State of the State Address to the 1966 New York State Legislature, 1966 January 5; Sound, Black and white, 32 minutes (Box 63, Reel AV 10623)
      Other Finding Aids
      2 inch videotape
      Program begins with 1 minute of bars and tones.
      Separated Materials
      A joint session of the New York State Assembly and Senate for the purpose of receiving the annual message of the Governor.
    - Senator Javits Nominating Speech, 1966 September 9; Sound, Black and white, 21 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 64, Reel AV 10624)
      No sound until 1:30. Program begins at 3 minutes.
      From the the 1966 New York State Republican Convention, Nelson A Rockefeller is nominated for Governor. Unedited footage at beginning of tape.
    - Phoney Taxes - Take 15 (edited), Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute 30 seconds; 2 inch videotape (Box 19, Reel AV 11509)
    - O'Conner - Upstate - Take 8 (unedited, close-up shot), Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 19, Reel AV 11508)
    - B.S. Thruway Stateside - Take 33, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 19, Reel AV 11507)
    - BS Narcotics - Take 11, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 30; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 19, Reel AV 11506)
    - The Bosses - Take 31, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 19, Reel AV 11505)
      Image is dark.
    - Brooklyn Narcotics - Take 26, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 19, Reel AV 11504)
    - Bossism Statewide - Take 9, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 30; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 19, Reel AV 11502)
    - B.S. Thruway Statewide - Take 7, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 30; Sound, Black and white, 75 seconds; 2 inch videotape (Box 19, Reel AV 11501)
    - BS Narcotics - Take 8, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 7; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 18, Reel AV 11498)
    - Question Card - Take 16, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 18, Reel AV 11497)
    - It Can't Happen Here - Take 21, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 18, Reel AV 11495)
    - Crime - Take 1, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 19; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 18, Reel AV 11494)
    - Crime - Take 37, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 18, Reel AV 11493)
    - Personal Medicaid - Take 34 (With NAR), Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 20; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 18, Reel AV 11492)
    - Brooklyn Narcotics - Take 26 (unedited), Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 9, Reel AV 11410)
    - Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot: Jacob J. Javits on Delegates - Take 2, 1966 September 30; Sound, Black and white, 3 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 9, Reel AV 11411)
    - Governor Rockefeller: Disclaimers, 1966 September 19; Sound, Black and white, 3 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 9, Reel AV 11412)
    - State University of New York - Take 31, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 10, Reel AV 11416)
    - Negative - Take 50, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 10, Reel AV 11418)
      Paid political announcement regarding Governor Rockefeller's ideas to assist mentally challenged people. Spot uses a negative film effect.
    - Why Does Governor Rockefeller Want To Be Governor Rockefeller Again? - Take 11, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 November 3; Sound, Black and white, 5 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 10, Reel AV 11419)
    - O'Conner - Upstate - Take 8 (unedited, medium shot), Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 17, Reel AV 11491)
    - Personal Medicaid - Take 24, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 10, Reel AV 11420)
    - Personal Medicaid - Take 22, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 10, Reel AV 11421)
    - Negative - Take 48, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 10, Reel AV 11423)
    - Phoney Taxes - Take 15 (unedited, medium close-up), Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 11, Reel AV 11425)
    - Arthritis - Take 60, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 10, Reel AV 11424)
    - Subways - Upstate - Take 10, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 30; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 11, Reel AV 11430)
    - Rockefeller: Wild Video for Disclaimer - Take 9, 1966 October 7; Sound, Black and white, 4 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 11, Reel AV 11431)
    - Subways - Upstate - Take 29 Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 11, Reel AV 11432)
    - Cartoons - Take 35, Rockefeller for Governor, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 12, Reel AV 11434)
    - Senator Jacob J. Javits on Frank O'Conner - Take 39, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 12, Reel AV 11435)
    - BS Narcotics - Take 30, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 12, Reel AV 11437)
    - Personal Medicaid - Take 48 (NAR on Camera), Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 19; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 12, Reel AV 11438)
    - Medicaid - Take 34, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 20; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 12, Reel AV 11439)
    - Bossism Statewide - Take 27, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 12, Reel AV 11440)
    - BS Narcotics, 1966 October 7; Sound, 2 inch videotape (Box 13, Reel AV 11448)
    - Crime - Department of Crime Control - Take 13 (unedited), Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 1 min. 20 sec.; 2 inch videotape (Box 13, Reel AV 11451)
    - It Can't Happen Here - Take 30, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 13, Reel AV 11452)
    - Personal Medicaid - Take 62, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 14; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 14, Reel AV 11456)
    - O'Conner - Upstate - Take 8, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 October 28; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 14, Reel AV 11457)
    - Crime - Department of Crime Control - Take 9, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 2 minutes; 2 inch videotape (Box 17, Reel AV 11490)
    - The Bosses - Take 29, Governor Rockefeller Campaign Spot, 1966 September 15; Sound, Black and white, 1 minute; 2 inch videotape (Box 17, Reel AV 11489)